<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unity on sheltron</title>
    <link>https://nshelton.github.io/categories/unity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unity on sheltron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 00:13:37 -0706</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nshelton.github.io/categories/unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Neonz AR</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/neonz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/neonz/</guid>
      <description>AR NFT Viewer In 2021, Sutu launched one of the first generative NFT series on the tezos blockshain, a 10,000 profile pic series called Neonz. I think this is one of the few great examples that demonstrates how to use web3 tech across platforms, while also being really cool art in its own right.
This was deveoped by the folks at Eyejack, I got on board to help them with some AR rendering effects for iOS and Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSMA302 Advanced Programming</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/csma302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/csma302/</guid>
      <description>My First Course In Fall 2021 I taught a class at Woodbury University in Burbank on some Advanced Programming techniques in Unity. This was in the Architecture School, aimed at non-computer Science majors who had already taken two semesters of Unity / gameplay programming. This was the first class I taught like this, and I learned a lot&amp;hellip; I made all the curriculum from scratch, and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty proud of it so with their permission I&amp;rsquo;ve made it freely available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life After BOB</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/lifeafterbob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/lifeafterbob/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Unity short Film What if an AI could do the job of living your life better than you?
Neural engineer Dr. Wong has installed an experimental AI named BOB (“Bag of Beliefs”) into the nervous system of his 10-year-old daughter Chalice. Designed to guide Chalice through the challenges of growing up in a volatile world, BOB confronts more and more of the conflicts in Chalice’s life on her behalf, while Chalice grows increasingly irrelevant and escapist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TopoChico</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/topochico/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/topochico/</guid>
      <description>Realtime Kinect visualizer experiments
Hooked up a Kinect Azure to Unity&amp;rsquo;s VFX Graph to explore some live realtime visuals for Lyell Roeder (Alt Fi) and Troy Everett - a Live improv ambient set
video   stills time delay Troy is always looping sounds and riffs from his viola. So I wanted to make a visual analog of that where we see multiple copies of the musicians over time, delayed by exactly a beat or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Weeknd</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/weeknd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/weeknd/</guid>
      <description>Live interactive broadcast on TikTok We went all out to stream a virtual interactive Weeknd concert to TikTok. The Wave tapped into the real time chat API to allow interactive voting moments. Unlike all the other waves though, The Weeknd is too cool to actually wear a mocap suit, so we got an actor to be him, raising some strange quesitons about the future of virtual performance and likeness…
But we ended up raising $350K for Equal Justice Initiative through merch sales!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Legend</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/johnlegend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/johnlegend/</guid>
      <description>John Legend live charity show
  After a brief coronavirus-induced break at Wave, we rented out a studio to set up a Yamaha electric grand piano and get the man JOHN LEGEND HIMSELF into the xsens suit to do a live performance.
We raised almost $10k for FREEAMERICA
 behind the scenes BOBBY was our mocap stand in for a lot of tests. And he CUT THE LINE at Whole Foods 1 hour before the set so that he could get John a WHOLE COOKED CHICKEN which we learned is the most important thing so that he can sing good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fractal Path Tracer</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/fractalpathtracing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/fractalpathtracing/</guid>
      <description>I decided to take my fractal rendering to the NEXT LEVEL by implementing a simple compute shader path tracer in unity.
Code Mostly Lifted from Three Eyed Games tutorial
Source Code on github
Temporal Reprojection But then I decided to reproject frames from the past into the current buffer to improve convergence, and make it pretty much realtime. Will add some more about this later
Renders </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rap Word Cloud</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/wordcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/wordcloud/</guid>
      <description>An Optimisaiton Journey. Client : Rap Research Lab
Rendering 5000 TextMeshPro meshes in 1ms for an interactive VR word cloudI started with a naive 5000 TextMeshPro gameobjects, which could take 30ms CPU and GPU, and made a new system that took 1ms CPU and GPU and still looked dope.
FunctionalityInteractive 3D visualization of words used in a corpus of rap lyrics (See Part 1)
Interface Features Left Thumb button transitions from Globe View to Word Cloud view Right hand controller has a “laser” which intersects with words to select them Clicking word with laser transports user to the word Words can also be selected with Right Hand controller Interaction point Selecting word with Right hand shows usage over time of the word and 10 similar words Timeline View Pressing both grips allows user to scale and rotate the word cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/growth/</guid>
      <description>Along with fractals, I also got really into growth algorithms, especially making them run in realtime. It seems like a perfect intersection of design and art with computer science and math.
Here are various realtime versions of some interesting growth algorithms I have seen over the years.
 Mesh based Mesh Splitting / Spring and attractive forces  Diffusion-Limited Aggregation   Voxel based Gray-Scott Anisotropic Dendritic Solidification  Mesh Based These involve splitting a manifold (1d or 2d surface) and then moving the nodes around in a higher dimensional space to minimise overlap</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Stirling</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/lindsey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 20:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/lindsey/</guid>
      <description>   Testing the suit! It didn&amp;rsquo;t work very well with the arms
IK constraints to make hands match violin (because all the mocap is live we can&amp;rsquo;t touch it up!)
Team  sheltron : technical director, mocap daniel sierra - unity technical artist aaron lemke - unity artist show director dare matheson - VFX, characters, environments mike krentz - art direction  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REZZ</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rezz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rezz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Senses EP release&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Pain</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/tpain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/tpain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;T-Pain&amp;rsquo;s School of Business feature at The Wave&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Light - Kizuna AI / W&amp;W</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/kizuna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/kizuna/</guid>
      <description>At the Wave VR we made a Music video for Internationally renown producers DJs W&amp;amp;W for their musical collaboration with japanese vtuber Kizuna Ai.
  We had to make this in like a week or two, so we Here&amp;rsquo;s some Unity Workflow Documentation:
Art Team Aaron Lemke, Dare Matheson and Daniel Sierra built this out of mostly kitbash assets and copious Unity postprocessing Kitbash Neo Tokyo Animation Data The Kizuna mesh and mesh came straight from Activ8 in MikuMikuDance format</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FractalFlames</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/fractalflames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/fractalflames/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fractal Flames&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magfest VJ</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/magfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/magfest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Super MagFest 2019 DJ battle&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OP-Z</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/op-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/op-z/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Unity Visuals pack for OP-Z multimedia synthesizer&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imogen Heap</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/imogenheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/imogenheap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VR Volumetric Music Video Experience for Imogen Heap&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See Without Eyes</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/seewithouteyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/seewithouteyes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Interactive VR Music video Experience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rpo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rpo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Making of TheWaveVR&amp;rsquo;s Distracted Globe&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ṛta</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/rta/</guid>
      <description>Free VR Fractal Visualizer &amp;amp; Manipulation Software for Vive
  Ṛta is the principle of natural order which regulates and coordinates the operation of the universe and everything within it. In the hymns of the Vedas, Ṛta is described as that which is ultimately responsible for the proper functioning of the natural, moral and sacrificial orders.
I am excited to share the next version of the FORM fractal visualizer, using a new compute shader surface calculation and rendering architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Flying Lotus Visuals</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/flylo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/flylo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;3D Visuals content for Flying Lotus and Strangeloop Studios&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKTUAL</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/aktual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/aktual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ASH KOOSHA show in TheWaveVR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRIMECRAFT viz</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/grimecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/grimecraft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VR Visuals in TheWaveVR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>N-FOLD</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/nfold/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/nfold/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hyper-Dimensional Odyssey&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FORM 0.0 beta</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/form/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/form/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Free VR Fractal Visualizer &amp;amp; Manipulation Software for Vive&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>artandvr</title>
      <link>https://nshelton.github.io/home/artandvr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 00:13:37 -0706</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nshelton.github.io/home/artandvr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Art and VR at HACK TEMPLE and The New Parish with Gaslamp Killer&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
